<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Usnish Majumdar</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Usnish Majumdar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 02:03:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Vaccines are not enough</title>
      <link>/post/2017/02/04/vaccines-are-not-enough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 02:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2017/02/04/vaccines-are-not-enough/</guid>
      <description>An illustration of Ebola stigma and treatment, drawn by the CDC.
Co-written with Christopher Cai, a friend and clinical trial coordinator at Massachusetts General Hospital.
Amid much fanfare, an international team of researchers recently reported the final results of the first successful Ebola vaccine trial.
While we should celebrate this result, we must also consider its value to those it was meant to help. Looking ahead, a capable response to future epidemics in West Africa will require both vaccines and sustained commitments to public health infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps into Lusaka</title>
      <link>/post/2014/08/24/steps-into-lusaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2014 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2014/08/24/steps-into-lusaka/</guid>
      <description>[EDIT 2.1.16 - I had the chance to look back on this. While this post is a hopeful one, it also reflects a kind of naiveté about NGOs and their role in development.]
We live in the house of a Korean ex-pat in Olympia, a diplomatic and upper middle-class community in Lusaka. Besides the frequent foreigner mistakes, the last three weeks of living here have been rather peaceful. When eight people live together in a two-bedroom house, privacy is fiction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conservatism &amp; the Internet</title>
      <link>/post/2013/12/14/conservatism-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2013/12/14/conservatism-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>Lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve caught myself thinking back to what the internet was like when I was a little kid in middle school (circa 2007). Back then, the web was this cool little place that lived inside my computer, one which I&amp;rsquo;d occasionally log into to mess around with friends on a little forum we&amp;rsquo;d created for ourselves. We were a glorious band of geeks, a bootstrapped &amp;ldquo;game development team&amp;rdquo; with a number of entertaining pursuits, including but not limited to: a friendly 3D modelling competition featuring a Honda Odyssey and half of a Lamborghini Murcielago, a space shoot-em-up game built completely in-house from visuals to music, and a number of entirely random philosophical discussions (middle schoolers on philosophy?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>